Is there anything you can do for us?
All right. Okay.
I can go defend her.
Jolyne Cujoh, that is.
I'll take care of this geezer!
Southeast, 127 degrees,
30 minutes and 20 seconds.
This time, you will not survive.
Face southwest, 225 degrees, 0 minutes.
F.F., it's behind you!
I said, your enemy is the geezer!
His arm flew behind F.F's head!
Was that a coincidence just now?
That prisoner's glasses flew up
and stabbed F.F.'s face!
Unlucky direction.
I'm starting to understand it.
He's using feng shui.
There is a principle called feng shui
in East Asia.
Kenzou uses that dragon-like Stand
to choose his direction of attack.
F.F., this area is your worst luck.
Just above your left ear.
My attack overlapped with
your orientation of death!
F.F.!
No… this is seriously bad.
Stop.
You cannot save them.
The direction of our worst luck
exists for you and me as well.
And once it's decided,
no living being can escape it.
It was proven to us just now.
Their next target
will be you.
No.
I'm not talking about their head
getting chopped in half.
I'd rather that
their head bleed profusely.
It's worse that
they're barely bleeding at all.
All the damage has depleted
the water levels in their body.
The plankton in their body
are starting to die off!
I'm glad it's not gushing out.
But that was the unluckiest direction,
without a doubt.
EPISODE 18: ENTER THE F.F.
What? Return to me, dragon!
That almost finished you off, geezer!
Never…
Never again!
Never will I set my foot off of
the direction of safety!
Shit, he escaped to a safe area.
But…
I'm starting
to understand the orientations,
and ways around it!
A mirror… I need to make a mirror!
If only there was a mirror midair,
then I can reflect that dragon on it.
I can trick Kenzou into stepping
towards a fake direction of safety.
Then, I'd have a chance to beat him down.
But first, I must have water.
I can make a mirror out of water.
I need water to heal
from all the damage too,
but right now, I need to replenish
on water to create a mirror midair!
In the past, over 30,000 believers
followed my teachings
and walked in my steps.
But ever since I came to this prison,
my life has changed.
I'm mocked.
Everyone mocks me and laughs at me.
Even a pedophile
who kidnapped children ridiculed me.
Forty years…
I've suffered this for 40 years!
I was once respected!
Forty years ago, I basked in glory!
And those days will come again.
The feng shui which saved me
from the ravaging fire
has now taken form as my Stand!
I will reign as Founder once again!
Though I may fail to break out of here,
fervent followers will return to me!
After I finish you off, that is!
Now, meet your end!
Drake's Dream!
Reveal to me
the direction of the finishing blow!
F.F., just beyond the stairs!
There's a fire hose!
Hey, you.
Don't just stand there and explain things.
Go help F.F.!
You have a Stand, don't you?
Fight with F.F. to finish off that geezer!
Only if F.F. dies.
My terms do not include helping F.F.
Our deal only extends to saving you.
Besides, F.F. themself
said they don't want any help.
When they saw your injuries,
F.F. directed me to protect you from
the enemies in this Disciplinary Wing.
Where is it?
How do I make water come out?
Where is the valve?
Don't come here.
This area contains your worst luck yet.
Guard against it at all costs.
Or else, you will be dealt
a decisive and fatal blow.
You don't have time to drink water!
Of their own volition?
F.F., what the hell are you doing?
The attack against you has been decided!
What are you thinking?
F.F. must have water above anything else.
Even in the way of a decided attack
or the zone of worst luck.
They got rid of their arms on purpose
so that they could fit into that hose.
They did it! They finally have water--
That's your own arm.
Here comes the assassination feng shui.
Looks like you desperately wanted water,
but you will never be at an advantage
from now on.
My attack will only bring you
the worst luck.
Such is the assassination feng shui,
Drake's Dream!
That's what it means
to have your fate sealed!
They couldn't reach water.
They didn't even touch it!
What happens now?
Underneath this Disciplinary Wing
is the execution room.
The State of Florida
permits the death penalty.
Two or three prisoners a year
are executed on
a 2,800-volt electric chair.
D-damn…
I was so close to touching the water.
But I did bust the pipe.
I need to reach the water
upstairs somehow.
At this rate, I'll…
Plankton like them
would perish in an instant.
Shit!
This chair, it can't be!
What? Don't tell me it's already on!
Does that sound mean
the electricity is ready to run?
Bullshit!
I won't let it run!
Let's see what kind of an end
you'll meet with my attacks.
Anyone can predict the outcome
of this situation at this point.
Before it turns on,
I will get the drops of water
dripping from the ceiling!
Looks like your place on that chair
was already decided by fate.
Take this!
Behold, you will never obtain water.
And that was right on time.
You will now meet your end!
STAND NAME: F.F.
STAND MASTER: F.F.
F.F.!
The absolute orientation of attack
and flawless direction of defense.
Assassination feng shui.
It took 40 years,
but I can now say I have mastered it.
The Founder reigns again!
With this, I'll go down in history
as a Buddha equal to Shakyamuni!
You know I'm supposed to stay neutral.
I'm in no position
to tell you this, geezer.
But F.F. finally got
the water they wanted.
If it weren't for your kick,
they wouldn't have had any.
You ran a little too much,
you 78-year-old man.
You can't help but sweat when
they had you running all over the place.
And your perspiration
became the water they needed.
F.F. made a mirror out of your sweat.
With enough sweat
to fill a third of a cup,
they can form a floating mirror.
What I'm saying is that
you're seeing my reflection.
So you are by no means standing
in the orientation of safety.
It's a draw.
The only chance
at defeating assassination feng shui
is a draw.
They have braced themself for this moment.
That's right, take this.
I'll share this unluckiest fate with you!
The direction of safety…
F.F.…
It's over.
On to the next.
You wanted to look for the bone, right?
We must start thinking ahead.
At the least, you won't fall victim
to Kenzou's assassination feng shui now.
It was indeed a formidable Stand.
F.F.!
Inconceivable.
Jolyne Cujoh, what are you doing?
Your body has suffered
more damage than you realize!
The colony of plankton inside F.F.'s body
has already been wiped out
by 2,800 volts of electricity.
You know better than anyone else!
B-But the dragon…
The dragon is still here!
They must have let go of him
a moment too early.
Or it could be that plankton
are more susceptible to electricity
than humans.
Kenzou is still alive!
Wait! You cannot manifest
your Stand with that body!
Has revenge driven you mad?
I won't let him stay alive like this.
Stone Ocean!
You cannot hit me.
I will finish you and reign
as the Founder once again!
I see it now.
So that's the direction of safety.
So I see.
You were after Kenzou's
direction of safety.
Once you identified
the direction impervious
from every attack,
then F.F., who scattered along with
the mirror, should be safe in this spot.
The plankton there should've been
safe from the 2,800 volts.
You attacked him to find this exact spot.
F.F. survived.
Good grief.
How could this be?
Jolyne!
You think you've won now, do you?
You think you have defeated me?
Jolyne Cujoh.
There is no change in my plans
to defeat you.
You haven't noticed, now have you?
You have already…
stepped inside
my assassination feng shui's direction!
My thread is inside the dragon!
The attack is absolute!
Your worst luck has now been decided!
It doesn't matter how I choose to attack,
because your defeat is already decided!
I won!
Now, kneel before me!
The Founder's reign cannot be altered!
What? Hey…
I dealt a blow, didn't I, Drake's Dream?
Assassination feng shui is absolute.
My deadly kick should have
defeated Jolyne, isn't that right?
Yeah, she couldn't dodge your deadly blow.
Then how is Jolyne unscathed,
while I'm clinging to this fence?
What?
Dragon, show me the direction of safety…
Come now, dragon, why are you moving away?
Tell me the direction of safety!
Why won't you come closer?
I want to ask that myself.
You are the one getting farther away.
You let go of that railing,
and now you are falling down.
Why are you just blabbering?
I said, tell me the direction!
I told you,
you are the one getting farther away.
Geezer, look at your own legs.
Something is really wrong with it.
There's something off about them.
You could have gotten attacked
when you kicked Jolyne.
Oh, that's…
What the hell?
That's not her thread Stand!
What is that Stand emerging
out of Jolyne Cujoh's body?
Diver Drive.
I submerged it into her body.
Though the attack on Jolyne was decided,
it protected her precisely
at the moment of your blow.
What the hell?
This man who came with F.F.,
Anastasia.
He put his own Stand into my body
and destroyed Kenzou's legs in an instant.
His bones and muscles
were entirely disassembled.
They were then rearranged
into this spring-like shape.
It is now a suspension
made of meat and bones.
However, Kenzou is not feeling any pain.
But I don't feel pain either,
thanks to that Stand that
manipulated the guards into fighting.
But…
Even my hips!
I need the direction of safety, dragon!
I can't reach it!
I'm coming your way!
Is he really an ally?
He's capable of dealing
such terrible damage.
Just who is this man?
That's it. I love that.
Yes, I want you to gaze at me more.
Look at me with those eyes.
The direction of safety is northeast
and your lucky color is cerulean blue.
But you know… I think you're done for.
You sure aged a ton in a fight
that lasted a few minutes.
KENZOU (78 YEARS OLD)
STAND NAME: DRAKE'S DREAM
BEYOND RECOVERY
Are you okay, Jolyne?
Yes… The pain is hitting me
all of a sudden.
But I have to find the bone
and the small man who picked it up.
Wait just a moment.
I can fill your wounds.
Hurry.
I have to get it back soon.
My father's disc.
Subtitle translation by: Megumi Hunter